hicksphoto.com 2017-12-25

# Foliolink.com

### Privacy Policy  
_Last Modified: Feb 18th, 2015_

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use identifiable information regarding our customers and users of our websites and services. 

Throughout this Privacy Policy, "we" refers to InfoSource, Inc, which operates under the trade name of ISProductions®. This Privacy Policy applies to all products, services, and websites of InfoSource and ISProductions®, including but not limited to our FolioLink™ and FolioArchive™ services. 

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at: 

Privacy Matters  
ISProductions  

### Information We Collect

You are not required to provide any personal information on the public areas of this website. In order to provide our full range of services, however, we may collect certain information from you. Our primary goals in collecting your information is to provide you with the products and services available through out site, to communicate with you, and to manage your registered user account, if you have one. 

**The types of information and the means by which we collect it are as follows:**

  *  **Information that you provide:** In order to establish your account, participate in various online programs and surveys, or visit the sites of customers we host, you might be asked to provide certain personally identifiable information to us such as your name, mailing address, e-mail address, and phone number. If you choose to purchase products or services, you will be asked to provide a valid credit card number and expiration date along with billing and shipping address information. You can choose not to provide this information but then you might not be able to participate in some of our services or offerings.
  * **Cookies:** A cookie is a small amount of data sent by our website and stored on your computer's hard drive that our website can read and which helps us keep track of how you use our website. We do not use cookies to collect personally identifiable information. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies. If you do not wish it to do this, you can use your browser's editing function to instruct your browser to stop accepting cookies or to notify you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.
  * **Web Beacons:** We also place small tracker codes or "beacons" on some of the pages on our website, in online advertising with third parties, and in our e-mail. We use these beacons, in connection with cookies, to collect non-personal data on the usage of our site including but not limited to the date and time of the visit, the pages visited, the referring web page, the type of browser, the type of operating system and the domain name of the visitor's Internet service provider. This information is collected about thousands of site visits and analyzed as a whole. This information is useful, for example, in tracking the performance of our online advertising such as online banner ads and to determine where to place future advertising on other websites.
  * **IP Address:** We analyze IP addresses in the aggregate for system administration purposes and to gather broad demographic information. We do not link IP addresses to your computer's User ID, with the following exception: when you register to a Foliolink Archive or Guestbook to track visits and prevent fraudulent resource utilization and when you place an order using our online checkout process we record your computer's IP address with your order to help us identify fraudulent credit card use. We may share this information with the financial institution that issued the credit card with which an order was placed, or with law enforcement authorities if we determine, or are notified, that the use of the credit card was fraudulent.  

  * **User communications:** When you send email or other communications to us, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.  

  * **Log information:** When you access our services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. Also, in order to protect you from fraud, phishing, and other misconduct, we may collect information about your interaction with our services. Any such information we collect will only be used to detect and prevent fraud or other misconduct.  

  * **Affiliated sites:** We offer some of our services in connection with other websites. Personal information that you provide to those sites may be sent to us in order to deliver the service. We process such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies.  

  * **Links:** We might provide links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising.
  * **Marketing efforts:** Some of the online technologies we use to advertise our services rely on third party remarketing or similar online advertising solutions. This means our third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to our website or client's websites (i.e. part of the FolioLink Network). You may obtain information about how you can opt out of Google's use of cookies by visiting Google's [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads). Alternatively, you can visit [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

  * **Other sites:** This Privacy Policy applies to our services only. We require our hosted customers to adhere to this Privacy Policy, but we do not exercise control over the sites linked from within our services. These other sites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.

### Information Sharing

**Your personally identifiable information will not be rented or sold to a third party. We may share your information as follows:**

  * When we have your consent. This will require you to opt-in before we can share any sensitive personal information
  * With companies who work on our behalf. From time to time, we contract with certain trusted third parties companies to support business functions on our behalf and provide services to us. These can include, without limitation, order processing, maintenance, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We will share your personally identifiable information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services, and only pursuant to binding contractual obligations requiring such third parties to maintain the privacy and security of your data.
  * With another office and/or affiliate of ours for purposes of service support, maintenance, or protection
  * With government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims, legal process (including subpoenas), to protect our property and rights of those or a third party, the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, or legally actionable activity, or to comply with the law.

###  Your Choice to Share Information

  * If you add people to your FolioLink contact manager or send postcards invitations, we will send an email to your list of recipients containing the URL to your images and/or an opt-in confirmation. Please note that your recipients can then forward the email containing the URL to other parties, if they choose. We uses the email addresses provided (including those in your address book) only to facilitate your image sharing activities and for no other purpose. We will not use the addresses described in this section for any other purpose and will not disclose the addresses you provide to any third party.
  * If you choose to share your Images via third party services, access to and use of the photos and the information you provide to the third party service will be governed by the terms of the third party services, and the password protections you established on Gallery may/will not apply. We are not liable for any access to, use of or disclosure of any photos or information you provide to third party services, or on public areas.

### Information Security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

### Keeping Your Information Accurate

We have a legal obligation to see that your information is kept accurate and up to date. Please assist us to comply with this obligation by ensuring that you inform us of any changes to your information. You have the right to request details of the information we hold about you and to delete or rectify any inaccurate information about you by sending us a written request to [privacy@isproductions.net](mailto:privacy@isproductions.net "Contact Us")  

###  Children's Privacy

The Site is not directed to persons under 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@isproductions.net](mailto:privacy@isproductions.net). We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal identifiable Information, we will delete such information from our files. 

### Widgets and Sharing Services

Some FolioLink sites may include third party widgets to gain access to popular bookmarking and sharing services. For example FolioLink uses the AddThis widget and third party cookies from Google Analytics and others. The following is a list of third party services that may be used in FolioLink and their links to their Terms of Service:

**Google Analytics Cookies**

This site uses Google Analytics, and their Third party cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use this site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. Find out more about the Google Privacy Policy [here](http://www.google.com/intl/en_uk/policies/privacy/).

**Facebook Cookies**

This site uses a Facebook Like Box, and uses Facebook's cookies to allow you to log in to your Facebook profile and 'Like' our Facebook page. Facebook cookies are also used when using the AddThis Social Sharing buttons. Find out more about the Facebook Data Use Policy [here](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/other).

**AddThis Cookies**

This site uses the AddThis widget to allow you to easily share content across Social Media networks, email etc. These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors are sharing this site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including number of shares of each page, and where the pages have been shared. Find out more about the AddThis Privacy Policy [here](http://www.addthis.com/privacy/privacy-policy).

**Twitter Cookies**

These cookies are used to allow visitors to share pages on this site via Twitter. These cookies are created via the AddThis Social Sharing buttons. Find out more about the Twitter Privacy Policy [here](https://twitter.com/privacy).

###  Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page.
